<package>
	<id> com.wavelink.bundleidsxi</id>
	<name>BundleIDsXI</name>
	<version>1.1.0-1</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>11.0</miniOS>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
		<package>mobilesubstrate</package>
		<package>AppList</package>
	</dependencies>
	<shortDescription>TD’s updated fork of BundleIDs for iOS 11+ devices.</shortDescription>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description>This app allows you to see the Bundle ID's of all the applications installed on your device. This app was originally by @NoahSaso. Sadly it appears that he has since gone inactive around a year ago and the app was only ever compiled for 32-bit devices. I figured this would be a relatively easy first attempt at jailbreak projects seeing as I have never really worked in this scene but have a little bit of coding knowledge from other types of small personal projects.  An absolutely HUGE thanks to @Skittyblock and @TheTomMetzger for all of their help in getting this update working and tested. I hope you all enjoy it even though it is a relatively small project. And finally a huge thanks to @xerusdesign for making the amazing new icon. If you would like to stay up to date with future updates to this package or possible new packages from me, please leave a follow over on my Twitter @TD_Advocate. Staying true to the original project, I have made my update open source for all to take a look at and even help me learn by helping me update the app further. You can check out my fork of the app at this link here. I have listed all of the changes that have been made from Noah's last build of the app below to show what all is new.
		</description>
		<description><![CDATA[
		Updates from Noah's last build:<br/> 
		-Support for all iOS 11-11.4 beta 3 devices and firmwares<br/>
		-Removed all new iOS 11 "applications" that are never actually seen by the user (let me know if I missed any or hid ones that I should not have)<br/>
		-Full iPhone X support<br/>
		-Changes to alert views<br/>
		-New "Copy All" feature<br/>
		-Brand new icon<br/>
		-Minor code changes to remove deprecated code<br/>
		]]>
		</description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot>
			<description>Real screenshots will be added asap!</description>
			<image>shot1.JPG</image>
		</screenshot>		
		<screenshot>
			<description>This is a description for screenshot 2. It's another Cydia!</description>
			<image>shot2.JPG</image>
		</screenshot>		
		<screenshot>
			<description>This is a description for screenshot 2. It's another Cydia!</description>
			<image>shot3.JPG</image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
		<change>Initial rerelease</change>
		<change>Brand new app icon by @xerusdesign</change>
		<change>Updated alert views</change>
		<change>Brand new “Copy All” feature</change>
		<change>Code modernisations</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>/r/jailbreak</name>
			<url>https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak</url>
			<iconclass>fa fa-reddit</iconclass>
		</link>
		<link>
			<name>Source Code</name>
			<url>https://github.com/tdadvocate/BundleIDsXI</url>
			<iconclass>fa fa-github</iconclass>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>